You know, the charge of loitering was created to keep black folk from gathering.
And some would like to convince you that that would be because, well, when black folk gathered, they made plans.
They were violent.
When black folk gathered, they revolted.
They're not wrong.
The Black Panthers was formed at Merritt College.
The Student Nonviolent Coordinating Committee, SNCC, was formed at Fisk University.
And the Black Campus Movement, I think it was from like 65 to the early 70s, was a bunch of black folks on campuses all over the nation.
PWI, the NHBCU saying, yeah, we're going to need to get classes that are specifically about African-American studies since we don't ever learn about none of this.
We're also going to need some black student unions.
When we get together, the multi-pronged approach to liberation happens like Voltron.
I just want y'all to know that it doesn't have to happen on the college campus.
It doesn't have to happen in a church.
It can happen anywhere.
It can happen in a prison commissary.
And it will continue to happen everywhere, no matter how hard they try to stop it.